http://www.2ridetheworld.com/privacy-policy

HomeAboutRiders• Lisa Thomas• Simon ThomasTripBikesBooksContactSearch ResultsNewsJournalEuropeAfricaSouth AmericaNorth AmericaAsiaAustraliaTips n' TricksReviewsBikeGearLifestyleEventsWork with usDealer Events - ASKMediaPressVideoSponsorsOptionsI Want to HelpShopBooksPrintsWearablesFit4ADV
HomeEventsDealer Events - ASKUncategorisedPrivacy Policy
08 Apr2017
Privacy Policy
Share
Tweet
Share
Email
Written by 2ridetheworld.
Website Terms and Conditions of Use 1. TermsBy accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark law.2. Use LicensePermission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on the 2 Ride The World web site for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not:
modify or copy the materials; use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial); attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on 2 Ride The World's web site; remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or transfer the materials to another person or "mirror" the materials on any other server.
This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by 2 Ride The World at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.3. DisclaimerThe materials on 2 Ride The World web site are provided "as is". 2 Ride The World makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, 2 Ride The World does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.4. LimitationsIn no event shall 2 Ride The World or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on 2 Ride The World Internet site, even if 2 Ride The World or a 2 Ride The World authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.5. Revisions and ErrataThe materials appearing on 2 Ride The World web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. 2 Ride The World does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. 2 Ride The World may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. 2 Ride The World does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.6. Links2 Ride The World has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by 2 Ride The World of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user's own risk.7. Site Terms of Use Modifications2 Ride The World may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this web site you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use.8. Governing LawAny claim relating to 2 Ride The World web site shall be governed by the laws of the State of Virginia without regard to its conflict of law provisions.General Terms and Conditions applicable to Use of a Web Site. Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date. Since 2 Ride The World uses Paypal service to collect payment information, your individual credit card or any other payment information is not kept on our servers. We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. We will not intentionally sell, distribute or share member's private and personally identifiable information except in such cases 2 Ride The World engages a third party to help deliver services and/or products which are promised and advertised on our site. In such a case, the third party agrees to keep all member information confidential. We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
Google AdWords
This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven't completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone's past visits to the AdventureMotorcycle.com website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google's privacy policy.You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, and if you want to you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Prev
Next
Search
JOOMLA_ARTICLESJOOMLA_CATEGORIES
2RidetheWorld Newsletter Signup
Thank you! Please check your email and confirm the newsletter subscription.
Your subscription was updated
Sign up to stay in the loop!
Email *
It seems that you have already subscribed to this list.										Click here to update your profile.
